

Tasikmalava, Indonesia

🛘 (+62) 857-8799-5896 | 🗷 hiaribahtiar@gmail.com | 🌴 kewcoder.github.io | 🖸 kewcoder | 🛅 aribahtiar

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

## Summary.

I am currently working part time as a Frontend LMS at GetInclusive US-Edutech Company. 5+ years experience specializing in frontend development, vue is specialist, and web development. enjoy to customize all development environment. Interested in designing better problem solving methods for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools when needed

## Work Experience \_\_

**GetInclusive** LMS FRONTEND Oct. 2021 - Jun. 2022

· Create LMS using Vue Js

· Maintenence Vue Project

**Upwork** US,Kanada,Jerman,Hongkong

Apr. 2021 - Sep. 2021

Sep. 2017 - Feb. 2018

Indonesia

- FREELACE FRONTEND DEVELOPER
- · Maintenece Vue Js Project
- · Slicing Design to vue js
- · Maintenece Laravel Project

**CV Alphabet** Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

FULLSTASK WEB DEVELOPER Jan. 2019 - Des. 2020

- · Yucoding Academy, create website using laravel.
- Sim-BTH, maintenance for campus academy system.
- · SIMANTAP, create website for campus academy system, laravel and vue js project, laravel project.
- · SIKEREN, create website and mobile app for financial management in Islamic boarding schools, laravel and vue js project.

Project.co.id Indonesia

FREELACE WEB DEVELOPER Jun. 2018 - Des. 2018

· Bug Fixing and maintenece website

**INDOMOBBUS** Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

- Feb. 2018 May. 2018 • Maintenence Point Of Sale.
- · Add new feature.

**BONFIRE CREATIVE STUDIO** Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

FULLSTASK WEB DEVELOPER

- · Create Landing Page Organization.
- Create System for KTA management using laravel and bootstrap.

PT Klikquick Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

FREELANCE FRONTEND DEVELOPER Jun. 2017 - Aug. 2017

• Create Ecommerce website using html css and js and vue js framework

### **Honors & Awards**

#### **DOMESTIC**

2020 Top 25 Startup, ASMI Indonesia Indonesia West Java, 2017 3rd Place, WEB DESIGN LKS Indonesia West Java, 2017 3rd Place, Graphic Design PETA Unsil

BYUNGJIN PARK · RÉSUMÉ JUNE 29, 2022

## **Presentation**

High School Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

PRESENTER FOR <WEB DEVELOPER SHARING>

• Introduced the history of web technology

Nov. 2019

# **Program Committees**

2019 **Founder Startup**, Hackathon Startup Unpad

Founder Startup, Hackathon Startup Coop

Indonesia

S.Korea

**Education** 

2019

Siliwangi University)

Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

FACULTY OF ENGINEERING, DEPARTMENT OF INFORMATICS

Aug. 2018 - Now

# **Extracurricular Activity**

BEM Unsil Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

MEMBER

• Create Web Organization

• Create Mobile App

Jun. 2020 - Jun. 2021

Indonesia

**Creative Developer** 

CORE MEMBER & PRESIDENT AT 2018

Jun. 2018 - Jan. 2019

• Sharing about web development.